A Guide to the Records of the Office of Academic Affairs, 1961-1977 (bulk 1965-1976)
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series XVIII: State Council of Higher Education for Virginia (SCHEV), 1970-1975
  - SCHEV - Proposed New Degree Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - SCHEV - Research and Development Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - SCHEV - Space Standards, 1970-1971 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - SCHEV - General Correspondence (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 10-11)
  - Instructional Programs Advisory Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Proposed New Degree Programs (2 folders), 1971-1972 (Box 60, Folder 13-14)
  - SCHEV (3 folders), 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 15-17)
  - SCHEV - Instructional Programs Advisory Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Proposed New Degree Programs, 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Research and Development Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - SCHEV (6 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 21-26)
  - Dunn/Little Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Virginia Plan, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - SCHEV, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 29-32)
  - Instructional Programs Advisory Committee (3 folders), 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 33-35)
  - Virginia Plan, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 36)